firstbanknigeria.com 2016-09-12

# First Bank of Nigeria Ltd. » Privacy Statement

You are here: [Home](https://firstbanknigeria.com/) [](https://firstbanknigeria.com/) » Privacy Statement 

## What this Privacy Policy Covers:

This Privacy Policy covers First Bank of Nigeria Plc's treatment of personally identifiable information that you submit through First Bank of Nigeria Plc web site, and the use of First Bank of Nigeria Plc's on-line/website services and contents (which on-line/website services and contents are hereinafter jointly called "the Service"). This policy does not apply to the practices of companies or subsidiaries that are affiliated to First Bank of Nigeria Plc. All subsidiaries have separate Privacy Policies.

## Privacy Policy:

### **Information Collection & Use**

When you complete any form on First Bank of Nigeria Plc website, it is normal that we ask for such information as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you fill the form on our website and submit the form, you are not anonymous to us anymore.

### **Information Sharing & Disclosure**

First Bank of Nigeria Plc will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. First Bank of Nigeria Plc may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * The law requires it of us;
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate any part of the First Bank of Nigeria Plc Privacy Policy.

The customers shall not disclose to any other person, in any manner whatsoever, any information relating to First Bank of Nigeria Plc or its Affiliates of a confidential nature obtained in the course of availing the services through the website. Failure to comply with this obligation shall be deemed a serious breach of the terms herein and shall entitle First Bank of Nigeria Plc or its Affiliates to terminate the services, without prejudice to any damages, to which the Bank otherwise may be entitled.

First Bank of Nigeria Plc will limit the collection and use of customer information only on a need-to-know basis to deliver better service to the customers. First Bank of Nigeria Plc may use and share the information provided by the customers with its Affiliates for providing services and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees for such services, and notifying or contacting the customers regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary to disclose the customer's information to the Affiliates of First Bank of Nigeria Plc who will be required to agree to use the information obtained from First Bank of Nigeria Plc only for these purposes.

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

First Bank of Nigeria Plc may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our website.

## Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions complete the [Contact Form](https://firstbanknigeria.com/contact-us/contact-form/).
